{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Window Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46356/":{"taskOID":46356,"originalTaskOID":46356,"setID":1151,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":200876,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Repair Required","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of repair work is required?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":19769,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Glass","answerDisplayText":"Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19770,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Frame","answerDisplayText":"Frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19771,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Frame \u0026 Glass","answerDisplayText":"Frame \u0026 Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200877,"questionDisplayText":"Items Requiring Repair","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"List all the problems you need repaired: (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":19772,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install New Glass","answerDisplayText":"Install New Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19773,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Glass is loose","answerDisplayText":"Glass is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19774,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Water leaking around glass","answerDisplayText":"Water leaking around glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19775,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Moisture between panes of glass","answerDisplayText":"Moisture between panes of glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19776,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Broken latch","answerDisplayText":"Broken latch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19777,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Block and tackle (pulley)","answerDisplayText":"Block and tackle (pulley)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19778,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Crank Malfunction","answerDisplayText":"Crank Malfunction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19779,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Window Sticks","answerDisplayText":"Window Sticks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19780,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Need Screens","answerDisplayText":"Need Screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19781,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Hinge","answerDisplayText":"Hinge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19782,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Window is jammed","answerDisplayText":"Window is jammed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19783,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Water damage around frame","answerDisplayText":"Water damage around frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19784,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Deteriorated wood","answerDisplayText":"Deteriorated wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200878,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Window","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the style of window(s) that need to be repaired: (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":19785,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fixed (non-opening picture window)","answerDisplayText":"Fixed (non-opening picture window)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19786,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Casement","answerDisplayText":"Casement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19788,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bow","answerDisplayText":"Bow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19789,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Sliding Glass Door","answerDisplayText":"Sliding Glass Door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19790,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Garden Window","answerDisplayText":"Garden Window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19791,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Single-hung (lower half opens)","answerDisplayText":"Single-hung (lower half opens)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19792,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Double-hung (both halves open)","answerDisplayText":"Double-hung (both halves open)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19793,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Bay","answerDisplayText":"Bay","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19794,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Storm","answerDisplayText":"Storm","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19795,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"French Door","answerDisplayText":"French Door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200879,"questionDisplayText":"Window Frame Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Of what material are the window frames made?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":19796,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19797,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19798,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19799,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood Clad","answerDisplayText":"Wood Clad","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":200876,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Repair Required","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of repair work is required?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":19769,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Glass","answerDisplayText":"Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19770,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Frame","answerDisplayText":"Frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19771,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Frame \u0026 Glass","answerDisplayText":"Frame \u0026 Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":19769,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Glass","answerDisplayText":"Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19770,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Frame","answerDisplayText":"Frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19771,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Frame \u0026 Glass","answerDisplayText":"Frame \u0026 Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200877,"questionDisplayText":"Items Requiring Repair","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"List all the problems you need repaired: (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":19772,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install New Glass","answerDisplayText":"Install New Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19773,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Glass is loose","answerDisplayText":"Glass is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19774,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Water leaking around glass","answerDisplayText":"Water leaking around glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19775,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Moisture between panes of glass","answerDisplayText":"Moisture between panes of glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19776,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Broken latch","answerDisplayText":"Broken latch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19777,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Block and tackle (pulley)","answerDisplayText":"Block and tackle (pulley)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19778,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Crank Malfunction","answerDisplayText":"Crank Malfunction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19779,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Window Sticks","answerDisplayText":"Window Sticks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19780,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Need Screens","answerDisplayText":"Need Screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19781,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Hinge","answerDisplayText":"Hinge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19782,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Window is jammed","answerDisplayText":"Window is jammed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19783,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Water damage around frame","answerDisplayText":"Water damage around frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19784,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Deteriorated wood","answerDisplayText":"Deteriorated wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":19772,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install New Glass","answerDisplayText":"Install New Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19773,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Glass is loose","answerDisplayText":"Glass is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19774,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Water leaking around glass","answerDisplayText":"Water leaking around glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19775,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Moisture between panes of glass","answerDisplayText":"Moisture between panes of glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19776,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Broken latch","answerDisplayText":"Broken latch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19777,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Block and tackle (pulley)","answerDisplayText":"Block and tackle (pulley)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19778,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Crank Malfunction","answerDisplayText":"Crank Malfunction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19779,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Window Sticks","answerDisplayText":"Window Sticks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19780,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Need Screens","answerDisplayText":"Need Screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19781,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Hinge","answerDisplayText":"Hinge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19782,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Window is jammed","answerDisplayText":"Window is jammed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19783,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Water damage around frame","answerDisplayText":"Water damage around frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19784,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Deteriorated wood","answerDisplayText":"Deteriorated wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200878,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Window","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the style of window(s) that need to be repaired: (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":19785,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fixed (non-opening picture window)","answerDisplayText":"Fixed (non-opening picture window)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19786,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Casement","answerDisplayText":"Casement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19788,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bow","answerDisplayText":"Bow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19789,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Sliding Glass Door","answerDisplayText":"Sliding Glass Door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19790,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Garden Window","answerDisplayText":"Garden Window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19791,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Single-hung (lower half opens)","answerDisplayText":"Single-hung (lower half opens)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19792,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Double-hung (both halves open)","answerDisplayText":"Double-hung (both halves open)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19793,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Bay","answerDisplayText":"Bay","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19794,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Storm","answerDisplayText":"Storm","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19795,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"French Door","answerDisplayText":"French Door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":19785,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fixed (non-opening picture window)","answerDisplayText":"Fixed (non-opening picture window)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19786,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Casement","answerDisplayText":"Casement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19788,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bow","answerDisplayText":"Bow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19789,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Sliding Glass Door","answerDisplayText":"Sliding Glass Door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19790,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Garden Window","answerDisplayText":"Garden Window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19791,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Single-hung (lower half opens)","answerDisplayText":"Single-hung (lower half opens)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19792,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Double-hung (both halves open)","answerDisplayText":"Double-hung (both halves open)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19793,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Bay","answerDisplayText":"Bay","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19794,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Storm","answerDisplayText":"Storm","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19795,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"French Door","answerDisplayText":"French Door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200879,"questionDisplayText":"Window Frame Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Of what material are the window frames made?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":19796,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19797,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19798,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19799,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood Clad","answerDisplayText":"Wood Clad","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":19796,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19797,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19798,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":19799,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood Clad","answerDisplayText":"Wood Clad","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564376531963pwspr010F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/46356/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46356,"taskName":"Window - Repair","taskDescription":"Window Repair","xmTaskDescriptor":"Window Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":281,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Window door Glass Frame mirror","textMessagingName":"Repr Wndowframe","rolloverLongDesc":"Note separate categories for glass replacement \u0026 window hardware repair.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes window glass and frames","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Windows Glass and Frames. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Home Window Repair Services - Glass, Frames, etc","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":9,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex, or you have a variety of small projects, please ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"request a Handyman","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Window Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Window Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Window Project","urlName":"Window-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Glass \u0026 Window Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Window,door,Glass,Frame,mirror,sliding","emcCategoryOid":-12080,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1151,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"isCookielessUser":true}